I was able to put in the next two colors of zaras.
please take care of me, please take care of me, please take care of me, please take care of me, please take care of me, please take care of me
Today we have Karen and Shinju.
We've already been to the Forest Garden Terrace four times today, outside.
You can tell by the way they're dressed. It's cold, you know?
We've already done the illumination this year, and today we're going to introduce the illumination that we do every year.
Let me introduce you to the illumination.
Today, I'd like to introduce you to this year's Eavins Collaboration Illumination, featuring Ms. Karen.
I'm sure you're nodding your head in agreement as to why we've invited Ms. Karen to this year's collaboration.
How is this year's collaboration going, Ms. Karen?
This year's illumination is a collaboration between Kanapei, a food sample goods artist, and Evin's illumination, and it's something you can only see here.
This year's illumination is a collaboration between Kanapei, a food sample goods artist, and E-bin's illumination, and it can only be seen here in Sendai.
That's amazing. I've never heard of it before.
I've never heard of it before.
I love her so much. I'm so confident.
I've heard about you for a while now.
I heard you were coming, but I didn't think you'd collaborate with Illuminations.
I was really looking forward to seeing what kind of clothes you would wear, so today, I'm going to have you two go around and share your love of food samples.
I was really looking forward to seeing what kind of clothes you would wear.
I'd like you to show your love to the fullest, and I'd like you to show your love to Illumination, and I'd like you to show your love to Illumination, because you have a song about it.
Do you have a famous song?
The first song you ever wrote was about illumination, right?
I wonder if she sings while watching the illumination when she gets in the mood.
Thank you very much.
Let's go ahead and take a look at today's video.
First and foremost...
Natto (fermented soybeans)!
This is amazing!
This is interesting.
The natto part of the food sample
It's a face frame!
That's amazing!
It's a food sample.
Yes! This is it!
This got a lot of attention on Kanape-san's SNS a while ago.
What? This?
Yes, Kanape-san is selling these goods.
You buy it and give it as a gift to someone.
And then he got a bunch of garbage in the mail.
My mother... It's a case.
It's a case.
It's a case that you can put "boo-boos" in. I see... it's very interesting.
It's a form.
This is what summer's all about, right?
Let's run, run, run!
What is that?
Huh?
Oh, but it looks good on you.
Really?
Yeah, I'm sure.
What? I'm so embarrassed.
I'm sorry, can I ask you one more time?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'll take a better look next time.
I'll be right here.
It's good... it's surprisingly clear from afar.
You can take pictures in different ways, so let's get closer.
It's nice. It's very luminous.
It's interesting how they do it.
It's fun to do it with a couple.
That's why they're lit up now.
It's interesting.
Look at this.
They have fishing here every year.
There's a cream soda stand here.
There's a cream soda pen stand.
This illumination is a cream soda.
I see.
And the color too.
Oh, cherries.
Yes, cherries.
This illumination is interesting.
It's a blessing.
The straw in the cream soda is a pentaten.
It's thicker.
That's funny. It's kind of funny.
I want one of these in my house.
Is this one of the best parts?
Food samples are...
It's playful.
I had a project to introduce food samples to Mr. Arin a long time ago.
I didn't like the real food samples.
I like them better.
I see.
It's disguised as something.
Disguised?
Or maybe it's half-eaten or spilled or something.
There are a lot of food samples like that, and I've been liking them a lot lately.
Yes, I see.
I see.
Then, Akanape-san is the most piercing, isn't it?
You have a lot of works like that.
I see.
Illumination.
It's so cute!
Isn't this Pearl's green?
I thought the song would come out now.
I thought the song would come out now... but it's not that easy...
Next, here's a shrimp tail brooch!
I don't know what it is, but...
I've finished eating.
I've finished eating it....
I don't eat shrimp tails.
I don't eat it. Is that normal?
I see... so you ate it, too.
But the color...
The color of a shrimp's tail!
It's the color of a shrimp's tail.
Boo-hoo! It's true! It's the batter and the tail, right?
That's right.
That's amazing.
It's a nice fusion.
Yes, it's true.
They do fit together.
I'm so happy.
It's like a dream collaboration.
It's true.
It's so cute.
A dream collaboration.
I thought you'd sing.
I see.
I thought a triple collaboration was coming.
Not yet.
Not like this.
Interesting.
It's playful.
Yes, it is.
It's like this... when couples go around together.
It's nice to talk about it.
It's fun with friends.
It's fun.
You can even wear a brooch!
It's cute.
It's like a prawn with a tail.
I said it like it's a common situation.
But it's not like that at all.
I said, "What kind of food do you eat?
Like, "There's chocolate on it.
I can understand that.
But a shrimp with a tail?
It's just a sloppy way to eat.
I don't think so.
That's funny.
How about this one?
What about here?
This is... what you said earlier about the food being on the verge of being eaten.
I said...
What a surprise.
Shrimp tempura with a tail.
You can see it spilled in the basement.
"Kenkako Namae" (Fighting child's raw egg)
It's a man's handwriting.
Not his wife's, but a man's.
Eggs flew off in a fight and broke on the laundry.
Yes. Interesting.
That's why he took the time to buy it. Yes, because they had a fight.
You've got a great sense of humor.
What's next? What's next? Cute soft serve ice cream.
It's so simple, it looks like he spilled it. Soft serve ice cream.
I think we should title it something... but I'm in a hurry... if it's true.
It's not just soft serve ice cream. It's only a food sample.
It stings when you drop it.
I saw this on social media. The bookmark for the cake?
That's right. What do you mean?
The part of the cake that you peeled off.
Yes, yes, the bookmark.
Give me this one.
I love it.
I love the idea.
You want to use it as a bookmark...
Interesting. Interesting.
Oh! It's like you spilled it....
I think KANEN-chan will like it. I love this kind of thing.
Natto cup version!
And top secret!
We don't write "top secret" in the proposal because we want to hide the title.
Next time you write it in red, it'll stand out.
It's funny! It's so realistic!
It's so realistic! It's so sticky!
I see... I love natto food service.
Another spilled version? This one's good too.
Spilled rice. Spilled parentheses.
Wow.
I love it. It's so real.
I'd love to have one of these in my house.
You hang these things up?
Yes, I do.
Yes, I do. I have a collection.
Wow.
I leave the staff samples on the table so my grandma will eat them.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's right.
That's dangerous.
I see.
Trust me.
It's a conversation starter.
Ha-ha-ha-ha. A conversation...
I'm kind of lonely.
Ha ha ha ha
I don't know.
I'm not an everyday person.
That's nice.
I see what you mean.
I've been having some family rumblings lately.
And then gradually...
Ha ha ha ha.
You don't have to talk about it.
I'm sure you and grandma have things to talk about.
It's funny, isn't it?
You know, when she spills something at the dinner table... like a deck of cards or something.
That's nice.
It's an art form, really.
I see.
Next...
Kinky beer glove compartment.
That's nice.
A glove compartment?
It's a good birthday present.
Maybe for your dad.
Yuna.
Hey, Yuna.
Beer color.
Yes, that's right.
You mean the bubbles are white?
You know, it's cute.
I see what you mean.
That's great.
It's nice with a little foam.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Are you sure you're drinking that?
No, I'm sure.
Oh, a little bit.
Oh, no, no, I know. I'm terrible at this. We both are.
Well, that's all right. Wow. Where do you put it? Here.
Where does it open? If you move that part, you can get a little bit of stuff in there right away.
You can put stuff in there. Does it open?
I wonder if it opens? Oh, yeah, it might.
Hey, this is real. This is real.
Yeah, it's like a freeze on the outside.
Shaved ice for us, too.
Lampshades. Lampshades?
It's glowing. What? It's for the house.
What? This is like a house light, Karen. What? It's awesome! What do you mean, like, house lights?
Like in your room? Oh, yeah, like a lamp in a room. Dark, dark, dark!
Dark, dark, scary! Well, Karen, you said yes. No, it's not scary with all this light in the room, is it?
That's why I'm trying to keep you occupied, Karen, because you're in the corner of the room and you like to beek.
No, I do.
But it sure is stylish.
This is where it's supposed to be.
It sure looks good on you.
Look at this, Kane-san.
It's nice.
So cute!
It's beautiful.
Wanna sing?
Not yet?
I thought she was going to start singing after that moment of silence.
I guess not.
Are you still there?
Still here.
If we sing here, there's no end to it.
We'll have to keep singing.
You'll choke.
It's too much work.
Om Light.
You're so cute.
Omright.
Omurite.
It's so shiny!
It's shining so brightly.
It's nice.
I like the naming sense.
I like it.
Omlight.
Oh, my God. - Oh, my God.
What color is it?
It's right in the middle.
Oh, my God!
It's yellow, red-yellow.
That's nice.
It's so cute.
This place is amazing.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Oh, my God.
Looks delicious!
Sendai's specialty corner!
Beef bowl, sasakama, belly meat and tobiko bento!
Wow!
Tobikko bento!
Never heard of it
Tobikko Bento
Certainly never heard of it
Never heard of it
It's like this is what I opened up at school... a dream... it's a food chample, so it's doable.
It's a lot of food! I can see why it's like food!
Beef tongue, bamboo shoots, rice threads, it's good, it's shiny!
I spilled all that on it.
Another simple title!
Wouldn't it be better if the yogurt had all these letters upside down?
I know what you mean.
It's nice.
What do you think, Mr. Kanape?
Yogurt would be nice if these letters were upside down.
Just upside down.
What do you think, Kimipei? Kimipae.
I like it, Kimipei.
You're so random.
Oh, come on.
I'm not saying it's good.
What are you, some kind of shady producer?
No, no, no...
Boo Boo! It sure brings back memories!
I've got this too... but it brings back memories.
This is a car and a necktie pin... and a car and a necktie pin... and a necktie pin... and a car and a necktie pin.
I can't go to work!
It's got my hand on it too!
I can't go to work...
Oh, I think that's what he means...
No, no, no, don't say it like it's one school, don't say it like it's a backstroke
Why don't you just pull right up...
That was a real...
boo boo
I'm using a golf marker as a sashimi to show you where your ball is.
I see what you mean. This is great.
This is great.
It's very realistic.
After dinner.
It's a glove compartment.
Oh, yeah.
I put my stamp in there.
What's the last name?
What's the last name on the stamp?
End.
Is that what it says?
Oh, my God.
I'm falling in love with it.
Because it's a collaboration.
With End Chain Evins.
Whose? Is it the boss's?
Oh, it's a great one.
He must be in some kind of trouble.
And the watch?
Isn't that the boss's watch, too?
He must be in a lot of trouble.
He's probably looking for it.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh!
I thought I forgot something.
This is great, isn't it?
Natto.
At the handle.
Touch this. It's his.
Oh, is that okay?
Maybe it's real.
It could be real.
Wow.
Smell that. Smell that.
What? Which way?
What was that?
What do you mean, "shhh"?
Oh, yeah, it smells great.
That's funny.
It smells good.
You were talking about how it's like it's never gonna get stolen.
Oh, I see.
That's true.
Oh, yeah, they would never steal it.
In fact, rather.
Rather, indeed.
Oh, wow.
Here they come.
Are you sure you want to do that?
This is it!
He told me.
The umbrella you can't take with you.
The idea of sticking it in a camera is really original.
That's really funny.
The decorations.
You can't really take pictures of this, can you?
I can't take any more pictures.
I can't take any more pictures!
I don't want this... no good... no good... no good... no good... no good... no good... no good... no good... no good!
4 passcases Endo chain mark
I wonder if he did it for this case, it's so cute.
I feel like a little girl man.
That foodstuff...
I don't know...
Boober!
I'm not a foodie, but I'm a weirdo. I'm running around adding food samples to my diet, and that's even weirder.
Ha-ha-ha, that's right.
With a card.
Boo-boo... the man of destiny... is this guy... who's got a big, fat loaf of bread... and he's gonna end up like this.
You're gonna wake up the voice.
What's wrong with that? It's not a good story.
I'm not good at stories.
Pressure!
Oh, no!
It's sweet, it's fun, and the bow is white, and the ears are white, and the bow is white, and the ears are white, and the bow is white, and the ears are white.
It's a bread...
In the middle.
That's how you take a picture.
It's bread!
You see, every year, there's this one. It's beautiful, isn't it?
Beautiful!
It's pretty.
It's like a zick video.
I'll keep the music... and put it into practice.
Illumination, illumination, illumination...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What the hell?
I made you do it, but you didn't like it.
It was really good.
Smile all of a sudden.
That was so good.
Please play this music as background music at E-WINGS!
Where is it?
I can't find it anywhere.
Take a picture of that.
Thank you very much.
It's beautiful.
It's really nice.
I love e-luminescence.
It's nice.
Rice ball lampshades.
That's why they're white.
That's why.
That's how it is.
It came from rice balls.
That's right.
Your groove is so small.
You're not flippant enough.
I want more of a groove.
You're a selfish girl.
Illumination.
The watermelon peeled it off.
I don't know the rest of the story.
What? Did you find anything?
Did you find the lyrics?
Illumination, illumination, illumination.
It's so beautiful.
Very pretty.
So shallow.
I'm sorry.
Illumination very beautiful
Illumination, illumination, illumination.
It's so sparkly.
The lyrics really stick with me.
Is that it?
Yes, sir.
I think it's a good song. It's not the lyrics.
This song is the reason I'm invited every year.
It's great.
I'm glad. Thank you.
It's beautiful.
Yes, so I went to see the collaboration of the innomination with Bibine and Kanape-san.
Interesting.
It was amazing. It was spectacular.
It was filled with the charm of food samples. And you can enjoy the illumination even more. You can only enjoy it here.
It's a six-turn collaboration that I never thought I would see.
If you go around with someone who likes food samples like Karen, they will tell you about their love for food samples.
It was an interesting world that we didn't know about.
Thank you very much for your time today.
I hope those who don't know about this event will enjoy it. I think it will be interesting not only for those who are interested like me, but also for those who are seeing it for the first time.
Isn't that the image of an old diner or something? Foodsoundl.
People who don't know about it. But it's a fun world. It's very deep.
There is a lot of room for imagination. It was fun. It was fun. It was fun.
How was the illumination? The illumination was in colors that matched the colors of the food samples,
Normally, the illumination would be like that, but it was really beautiful. Indeed.
It was the best collaboration. It's true, isn't it? It's also photogenic. It's fun, isn't it, taking pictures with everyone?
I heard that this collaboration of illumination can be seen until the end of February, so I hope everyone enjoys it.
I hope you enjoy it.
I want you to taste it.
The collaboration illumination can be seen on the 4th floor of the Mori no Garden Terrace, so I hope everyone will come and see it.
I hope you will come and see it.
Look at it.